hello sue
I'm Linda are you available for lunch today
no
David is unwell today and was unable to attend school
that's awful is it a cold
yes I believe so
he was suffering from a cough and a sore throat
my kid was also unwell last week
he was absent from school for 4 days
I hope David isn't too sick
there is a virus circulating
we must also maintain our health
I know to keep healthy
I've started taking additional vitamin C right
me too
I'm going to go out and buy something
do you want anything from the store
in fact I do
I couldn't go shopping
since I didn't want to abandon David
I get what you mean what do you want
could you kindly buy a chicken for me
I'd want to cook some chicken soup for David
okay I'll buy a chicken for you
thank you so much
okay I'll go to the shop after lunch
and we'll arrive at your place about two PM great
then I'll see you don't forget to stock up on vitamin C
I remember see ya